const questions = [
    {
        "question":"1.) JavaScript a _________ language?",
        "options":[
            "A.) Programming",
            "B.) Scripting",
            "C.) Application",
            "D.) All of the above"
        ],
        "answer":"A.) Programming"
    },
    {
        "question":"2.) JavaScript code is written inside a file with which extension?",
        "options":[
            "A.) .java",
            "B.) .script",
            "C.) .js",
            "D.) .javascript"
        ],
        "answer":"C.) .js"
    },
    {
        "question":"3.) JavaScript is a __________ side scripting language?",
        "options":[
            "A.) Client",
            "B.) Server",
            "C.) ISP",
            "D.) Browser"
        ],
        "answer":"D.) Browser"
    },
    {
        "question":"4.) What is the purpose of JavaScript?",
        "options":[
            "A.) To add style web pages",
            "B.) To execute database queries",
            "C.) To add interactivity to web pages",
            "D.) To merge HTML and CSS code"
        ],
        "answer":"C.) To add interactivity to web pages"
    },
    {
        "question":"5.) JavaScript code between a pair of script tags is called:",
        "options":[
            "A.) Inline",
            "B.) Nested",
            "C.) External",
            "D.) Referenced"
        ],
        "answer":"A.) Inline"
    },
    {
        "question":"6.) What is the correct way to declare a variable in JavaScript?",
        "options":[
            "A.) x = 100",
            "B.) variable x = 100",
            "C.) var x = 100",
            "D.) constant x = 100"
        ],
        "answer":"C.) var x = 100"
    },
    {
        "question":"7.) How do you remove the last element from an array?",
        "options":[
            "A.) remove()",
            "B.) deleteEnd()",
            "C.) snap()",
            "D.) pop()"
        ],
        "answer":"D.) pop()"
    },
    {
        "question":"8.) How do you call a function called sayHello?",
        "options":[
            "A.) sayHello()",
            "B.) execute sayHello()",
            "C.) call sayHello()",
            "D.) sayHello[]"
        ],
        "answer":"A.) sayHello()"
    },
    {
        "question":"9.) How do you remove a class using DOM manipulation?",
        "options":[
            "A.) removeClass()",
            "B.) element.classList.remove()",
            "C.) element.Class(remove)",
            "D.) element.deleteClass"
        ],
        "answer":"B.) element.classList.remove()"
    },
    {
        "question":"10.) Which naming convention should be used for identifiers in JavaScript?",
        "options":[
            "A.) UPPERCASE",
            "B.) camel_Snake_Case",
            "C.) camelCase",
            "D.) PascalCase"
        ],
        "answer":"C.) camelCase"
    },
    {
        "question":"11.) Which of the following objects is the main entry point to all client-side JavaScript features and APIs?",
        "options":[
            "A.) Position",
            "B.) Window",
            "C.) Standard",
            "D.) Location"
        ],
        "answer":"B.) Window"
    },
    {
        "question":"12.) Which of the following methods/operation does javascript use instead of == and !=?",
        "options":[
            "A.) equalto()",
            "B.) equals() and notequals()",
            "C.) equals=() and !=()",
            "D.) === and !=="
        ],
        "answer":"D.) === and !=="
    },
    {
        "question":"13.) Which Window object method is used to display a message in a dialog box?",
        "options":[
            "A.) alert()",
            "B.) prompt()",
            "C.) message()",
            "D.) console.log"
        ],
        "answer":"A.) alert()"
    },
    {
        "question":"14.) The setTimeout() method is used to:",
        "options":[
            "A.) Make the event sleep",
            "B.) Register a function to be invoked after a certain time delay",
            "C.) Invoke an event after a certain time delay",
            "D.) Time for iteration"
        ],
        "answer":"B.) Register a function to be invoked after a certain time delay"
    },
    {
        "question":"15.) Which of the following represents the content displayed in the window?",
        "options":[
            "A.) document",
            "B.) object",
            "C.) window",
            "D.) frame"
        ],
        "answer":"A.) document"
    },
]
